xtreamer.net 2016-11-28

# Xtreamer.Net - Privacy Polivy

**Our Promise to You Regarding Your Privacy  
****  
** Last Updated: April 11, 2009

At Xtreamer.net, we do more than protect your data. **We care about your privacy.**

As a global leader in HDD multimedia solutions, Xtreamer.net, knows the value of information and understands your concerns about privacy. As a result, we believe that you have the right to know how we collect and use your personal information. Xtreamer.net values your trust and respects your privacy — and is committed to protecting them.

 **How does Xtreamer.net gather and use customer information?**  
  
When you place an order, register a product, obtain technical support, download software, enter a contest or respond to our promotional campaigns we will gather certain personal information from you to respond to your request. For example, we will collect personal information such as your credit card number, contact information, billing and shipping address and use it to complete your order. In addition, we may use aggregate information to improve our website, but that information is never personally identifiable. (Follow this link for more detailed examples of whenXtreamer.net gathers information.) Xtreamer.net does not intend to collect information from children who are under the age of 18 in the European Union and Asia Pacific, or under the age of 13 in the United States and Latin America. If you do not meet these age limits, you should not provide information on this site and should ask your parent or guardian to do so for you. **What are cookies and how does Xtreamer.net use them?**  
  
Like most companies, Xtreamer.net uses cookies to customize our communication and provide you with better service. A cookie is a small data file that our website writes to your hard drive when you visit our site. That file may contain information that we use to track the Web pages you have visited or how often you've visited Xtreamer.net's site. The primary reason Xtreamer.net uses cookies is to prepare customized pages for you. However, a cookie cannot read data off your computer's hard disk. You can also set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, or you can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. **Will Xtreamer.net share my information with other companies or people?**  
  
Xtreamer.net will not sell, rent, trade, or lease your personal information for marketing purposes. We will only share information with third-party agents who provide services for our business operation. These agents must comply with our privacy policies and cannot use your personal data for any other purpose. Apart from this, we disclose personal information only in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal process; respond to any claims; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of Xtreamer.net, our customers, or the public. **Note to European Customers:**  

The information you provide us will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purpose of processing by Xtreamer.net, its affiliates and agents. By submitting your information, you agree to that international transfer.

 **How secure is the personal information I provide Xtreamer.net?**  
  
Xtreamer.net believes that it uses reasonable precautions, including a firewall, to protect your personal information. For Xtreamer.net's online store, web-based customer support, and product registration process, we use Secure Sockets Layer technology to encrypt the information you send us, when you use an encryption-enabled browser. **How can I manage my personal information or change my opt-in/out status?  
**  
For e-newsletters, software updates, and special offers, you may change your email address, change your preferences or opt-out from receiving Xtreamer.net communications at http://www.Xtreamer.net. These options are also generally included in the corresponding email communication.

If you have created an account at Xtreamer.net's online store, North American customers may change their personal information under the My Account header at the online store. Our European online store customers can also access their Account information under the online shop header, where they may view, edit, or delete personal information.  
If you have created an account at Xtreamer.net support site, you can manage and change your personal information and preferences by accessing your My Support account.

 **How can I contact Xtreamer.net if I have any further questions?**  
   
North American customers can find the information they need at the contact page.  
Latin American customers can find contact information at: http://www.Xtreamer.net  
European customers can find the information they need on the Contact Page.  
Asia Pacific customers can find the information they need at the contact page.

**Disclaimer :  
**  
Xtreamer.net is dedicated to continually improving its websites by adding new functionality, products, services and programs. Because of those improvements — along with the changes in the law, technology, and Xtreamer.net's business — Xtreamer.net reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. The latest version of our privacy policy will be available on our web site and will indicate the date that it went into affect. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use this website to make sure you always understand how your information will be used.

##  Get Involved

Want to become part of the 

##  Other resources & links

The following resources   
contain additional useful  
information about Xtreamer:

• [Official Shop](http://shop.xtreamer.net/)
